(Sharing Sorrows and Joys)
- It's good to see you! - Good to see you.
Today, we have Ahn Jae Hyeon and Lee Ju Seung with us.
It's been a while!
- Why did you stutter? - Gosh, Ju Seung...
I couldn't bring myself to mention him.
- You still can't remember his name? - Gosh, Ju Seung...
- It's your 1st time meeting? - Yes, it's our 1st time.
- We live in the same neighborhood. - This is your first time meeting?
- It's our first time meeting. - That's interesting.
Right.
You know what? This is the vibe I'm getting from them. He's HSM.
- Yes. - And he's FSM.
- What's FSM? - What's that?
- He's Healthy Seongsu Man. - My gosh.
- He's Frail Seongsu Man. - My gosh.
- FSM. - Yes, FSM.
- The shirt is too thick for summer. - My gosh.
- He must not be feeling well. - I'm wearing a sleeveless top too.
- It could've been bad. - My gosh, look at him.
Ju Seung, don't you think your tank top is too revealing?
- And... - That's a plunging neckline.
- I've been trying out... - What is this?
- many new things lately. - Did you change your style?
You suddenly became a guy with an attractive collarbone.
But it looks good on you.
Last week, we began a makeover series to greet spring.
- The Rainbow Refresh Special aired. - Yes.
Na Rae was the first one to go.
The F5 Special, also known as the Rainbow Refresh Special.
Part Two of the Special will be my episode. All right.
Let's go.
So there will be ten parts, right?
- No. - This is only the first part.
I heard it would run longer than "Tears in the Amazon."
- Great. - There's only one episode...
for "Hyun Moo's Tears."
- Just 1? - There's only 1 episode for that.
Okay.
(Rainbow Refresh Special for Spring)
"Moomoo's Update."
(Hyun Moo wakes up sluggishly.)
(He's still half asleep.)
(Should I have a glass of water?)
Hot water is coming out.
You woke up at 6am?
- Six in the morning? - Six in the morning?
Yes, in the morning.
Hot water is coming out.
(He gets a glass of hot water in the morning.)
Hot water?
(Then he presses the button for water at room temperature.)
(I'm tired since it's still early.)
What? What's that on his mouth?
- Is that a pacifier? - That's...
A pacifier? Don't you know how old I am?
I'll turn 50 soon.
He's not hesitant to speak up. Seriously.
His life will be refreshed for real then.
- It will be refreshed then. - That'd be amazing.
- That'd be amazing. - You'll be reborn.
I'm not Benjamin Button.
Don't you know how old I am?
(A newborn, Baby Moomoo)
I go to sleep with that on after I had laryngitis.
So my mouth doesn't dry out.
(He prepares a glass with hot and lukewarm water.)
(He removes the tape over his mouth.)
(He has a sip of the water.)
(Refreshed)
He must be drinking it because it's good for his throat.
- That's better than cold water. - Really?
That's trending these days. It's Yin-Yang Water.
- Yin-Yang Water? - What?
You mix hot water with cold water.
Then it's just tepid water.
- Tepid water is just tepid. - Okay.
- Mixing hot water with cold... - That's tepid water.
- That's Yin-Yang Water? - That makes tepid water.
Hashtag, Yin-Yang Water.
(Stubborn)
- People call it the Yin-Yang Water. - Like yin and yang energy?
- That's it. - That's where the name comes from?
Where is that trending?
You can check it out on social media.
(He's ridiculous.)
(He has another sip of the Yin-Yang Water.)
Why does he look so small today? He looks slim.
(Sighing)
Overall, my energy is low.
- I had laryngitis recently. - Gosh.
- Oh, no. - Gosh, "The Last Leaf."
- Gosh, seriously. That clip... - "The Last Leaf."
Getting laryngitis was no big deal.
But it shouldn't have lasted that long.
My immune system had weakened.
That's why it lasted quite long.
When I was younger,
getting a few shots at the hospital used to clear up whatever I had.
But my basic physical strength has been down lately.
It takes longer for my body to recover.
It affects my work too.
Even with the IV drip, it lasts longer than a week.
(I know how that feels.)
Age is one thing.
But I think it's because of my immune system.
I experienced the importance of having a strong immune system.
So this year,
I'll start a project to strengthen my immune system.
- Our immune system is so important. - That's everything.
Starting with food and my lifestyle habits,
I will look for ways to strengthen...
my immune system naturally.
- That's what I have in mind now. - Why are your eyes getting bigger?
- That's because he lost weight. - My face got slim.
Someone told me I resembled Heartsping.
- You do resemble the character. - Shih-Tzu-ping.
Your eyes are beautiful.
(Shih-Tzu-ping with beautiful eyes sips on the Yin-Yang Water.)
(After he builds his immune system with the Yin-Yang Water,)
(he trudges to the bathroom.)
(Flipping)
Is that for a lower body bath?
I guess he's going to take a bath.
(He hydrates his face with the face mask.)
- I use the face mask every day. - The face mask.
(He heads back to the kitchen with the face mask on.)
(Opening up)
(Rustling)
He's going to eat right away.
Is he going to eat ice cream?
(He grabs a bag of ice cubes from the freezer.)
(Thud)
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
- My gosh. - Oh, no.
- My gosh. - Just stay in bed!
Just stay in bed.
- You should sleep some more. - My gosh.
(Sleep some more, old man.)
(The ice pack lands on top of Elder Moo's foot.)
(Flinging it away)
(The pain makes him want to throw away everything.)
- That must have hurt a lot. - Gosh.
That hurts a lot.
"Rock-hard Ice."
You know that...
- those ice cubes are super hard. - Right.
- They're rocks, not ice cubes. - They are heavy too.
It felt like getting hit with a stone axe.
My gosh. Come on.
(Somebody save Moomoo.)
- Oh, no. - My gosh.
(He carefully picks up the stone axe.)
- That hurt so much. - Gosh, that's so annoying.
(He goes back to the bathroom with the ice?)
(Dumping)
(He pours the ice cubes into the tub all of a sudden.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
(Looking unsettled)
Do I have to go in completely?
(He plays a video on his phone.)
I wonder whose life he's going to steal this time.
(Laughing)
Jennie of BLACKPINK and Son Heung Min are hooked too.
- Jennie. - My gosh.
I hope he never watches Jennie's videos.
Jennie is one of the celebrities that dominates my lifestyle.
(Jennie)
I bought the same speaker she bought.
I also bought the soap for buttocks like Jennie.
- Why did you buy that? - What?
- What kind of soap is that? - What's that?
You only use the soap on your bottom.
My buttock skin improved.
(Disgusted)
- It's soft now. - My gosh.
It was effective.
Why do we have to know that his buttock skin improved?
You ought to know if you care about me.
(Oh, my goodness)
Then Jennie's video showed up on my algorithm again.
One of the healthy habits Jennie is hooked on these days...
is the cold plunge.
You dive into cold water.
- It's to improve my immune system. - Right.
(Including Lady Gaga,)
(Thanos, Hailey Bieber, Kevin De Bruyne...)
Thanos does it too.
- He did that too. - Gue Sung did it too.
Son Heung Min did it too.
I did hear that this was good for our health.
- Yes. He did that too. - Hee Chan did it too.
A lot of athletes must do it.
- I see. - This must be so trendy.
I did it before Jennie.
(Lee Ju Seung)
Ju Seung peed his pants after this.
Right. He did. The man who peed his pants.
(Even CODE KUNST did the cold plunge.)
I had never gone into a cold tub even at a sauna.
I hate cold water.
Cold water and I don't mix well.
I never did it no matter how many celebrities did it.
But Jennie said she tried it and it was effective.
So I thought, "Yes, it's all or nothing."
"Let's just try it once."
I tried it out for the first time solely because of...
Jennie.
Two minutes and thirty seconds?
Dear me.
But what about the intervals?
Jennie didn't talk about that.
Are you serious?
(I don't know about the intervals. But let me try it.)
(Shirtless)
Gosh, can't he shave his chest hair?
I can't.
(I see.)
(He gingerly walks toward the ice bath.)
(A shy pose)
(Removing)
(Coyly taking it off)
Why did he remove that so coyly?
(Checking out his face whenever he gets a chance)
(He dips his hand in the tub first.)
(Splashing)
My gosh. Darn it.
Why are you only wetting your chest hair?
So my hair doesn't get shocked.
(Carefully dipping his feet in one at a time)
- My gosh. - I hate cold water.
- You know, right? - You must go in at once.
- You must dive in at once. - Right. At once.
(He hesitantly tries to dip his lower body in the water.)
Gosh, come on.
- My gosh. - You must sit down right away.
(The chills reach all the way to his head.)
All right.
All right. Great.
(It's bearable now that he's in the tub.)
My goodness.
(He shivers every time the water splashes on his body.)
My gosh. I'm getting the chills. Oh, my.
(Tapping)
(Jennie said she stayed in the tub for 2 minutes and 30 seconds.)
(Then I'll stay in for 2 minutes and 30 seconds too.)
(He dips his whole body in a flash.)
- Seriously. It was so cold. - What's he doing?
(He barely manages to dip his body in the water.)
If I was going to do it, I wanted to do it properly.
My gosh, it's cold.
It felt like the cells in my body were waking up.
I screamed when I first went in.
That was the hard part. But once I was in,
I had better blood circulation than the time I did...
the lower body bath with hot water.
(Thanks to the cold plunge, his immune cells are on fire.)
(His immune system is strengthening.)
(In no time, the bathroom is filled with some healthy energy.)
My gosh.
Come on, faster. Just ten more seconds.
(His immune cells are making their last sprint for energy.)
His hairy body will get so cold.
(Time, move faster.)
I guess your body won't get used to the cold.
- The time moved so slowly. - It is moving slowly.
You need determination for this.
(It feels as if time had stopped during the last 10 seconds.)
Stop.
Thirty seconds.
Gosh, it's so cold.
(He gets up as soon as...)
(his 2 minutes and 30 seconds are up.)
It's so cold.
- But didn't it feel refreshing? - Right.
- It felt so refreshing. - Right.
- It woke you up, right? - That's great.
I felt blood circulating all over my body.
It's so cold.
(It was painful during the plunge, but it feels good afterward.)
(Grabbing)
It's so cold.
Gosh, it's cold.
This feels warm.
Gosh, it's warm.
- Yes, indeed. - My gosh.
- His eyes are full of life. - Look at his eyes.
- The swelling went down too. - Look at him.
I definitely felt my body changing.
It was like getting a brand-new body.
Let's say you don't feel good.
Doing a cold plunge makes your body feel brand-new.
- Right. - You know what I mean, right?
- It's... - You know since you're frail.
If I feel healthy even for a bit, that feels weird to me.
We think about how it'd be nice...
- to get our body fixed, right? - Poison is all over our body.
The bottoms of my feet are flat.
And there are always knots in my calves.
My calves always hurt even when I got massages.
I did that for 2 minutes and 30 seconds.
- And my calves felt so relaxed. - People say...
- toxins build up in calves. - Really?
- Massages take two hours. - Trying it once is worth it.
- It's worth it. - Yes, it is. Try it.
I strongly recommend it.
I think cold plunges will be a trend.
Jennie and Son Heung Min may have begun...
the trend globally.
But in Korea,
I will lead the trend.
The three of us have become the trend setters...
for cold plunges.
(The trend setter gets dressed after the cold plunge.)
I feel so refreshed.
I feel great. I feel refreshed.
It looks like he's going out to exercise.
- Is that a tennis outfit? - Right.
- It looks like his tennis outfit. - Right.
(Staring)
My gosh, it's 7am on Sunday.
I can't believe I'm up at this hour.
- It's really early. - Let's go.
Are you going to Sunday school? Why did you wake up so early?
(Pulling)
He'll play tennis.
Wait. It's a badminton racket.
(He goes out with a badminton racket around 7am.)
At 7am?
I'll play badminton.
I always wanted to play badminton...
when I played tennis.
- But... - His weight loss is visible...
with these old clips.
(Right?)
I met An Se Young once.
After watching her play, I became fascinated by the sport.
I always wanted to learn the techniques properly.
Recently, thanks to this guy's influence,
I started playing this sport.
I went out to play with my senior athlete.
- I signed up... - Who is it?
to the same school.
It's been 2 months. But I only attended 1 class...
because I caught laryngitis right after the class.
It's cold.
(He was sad he couldn't play badminton due to laryngitis.)
- Hey. - That's where...
- my senior athlete is. - It's cold.
- Wait. You're not playing outside? - It's in the basement?
It's an indoor court.
Badminton is an indoor sport.
- It can't be too windy. - Right.
You can't play badminton outside.
Gosh, you're here.
Wait, his voice...
(The mysterious senior was stretching.)
- He seems familiar. - He's an everyday athlete.
- Hold on. Gosh, what's going on? - Gosh.
- He looks so handsome in this clip. - The athletic man.
- Hold on. - He looks so handsome here.
Wait. He looks like a national athlete.
- He resembles the character... - Yes.
- in "The Prince of Tennis." - Right.
- He looks pretty good. - Yes.
(Fancy footwork is a given.)
- Gosh, he looks so professional. - Hey. My gosh. Oh, my.
(Twitching)
(He can deliver a strong smash shot too.)
His name is Lee Ju Seung.
Gosh, he looks cool.
I heard from our instructor that he was quite good...
only after playing for four months.
Oh, my.
(His shortening-distance technique trained his lower body.)
It's been a while.
His body moves swiftly.
(All kinds of martial arts built a strong upper body.)
He has the body of someone who exercises regularly.
(He also trained his mind with zui quan.)
What? That's you?
- He's good. - Why is he so good?
- Our instructor said he was good. - Gosh.
Remember the day Ju Seung dropped you off?
He played badminton before picking you up.
- Right. That's where he was. - Right.
It's close to my house.
- That's why he went. - That's where he was.
(Ju Seung drove Hyun Moo to the hospital...)
(right after playing badminton.)
- He played badminton before this. - What?
- But... - He must sign up to the class.
Then did you wake up at 6am too?
I also woke up at 6am.
Gosh, you're dressed in green too.
My gosh. That was telepathy.
(Two men dressed in deep green meet up to play badminton.)
You look good today.
But you don't look good.
You're saying that when we just met?
- Are you the instructor today? - I'm your instructor for the day.
- I can teach a beginner like you. - No way.
I can't believe this.
- I can handle you. - He must be really good.
- Why don't you grab the racket? - Yes.
You're good enough to teach him?
I learned the fundamentals.
I took only one class.
- You didn't learn the proper grip. - I did. What do you mean?
You grab the racket as if you were shaking hands.
You must be able to switch back and forth.
I can do it.
- Forehand and backhand. - Forehand and backhand.
(He focuses on practicing the grip with Coach Ju Seung.)
Let's warm up first.
- Let's stretch our legs first. - Okay.
You must always stretch your legs first.
- Why do you sound so confident? - You're no match for me.
- You're arrogant today. - No, listen.
Shuttlecocks are my friends.
He was bragging a lot.
You seem livelier than the time...
when you were shortening distance as Martial Artist Ju Seung.
I guess you're really good.
(Stretching)
Look at you.
- He was flexible at the temple too. - Right.
Can you do this stretch?
You can't do that?
- I had never been able to do it. - Gosh.
- I couldn't do it even as a kid. - My goodness.
(Struggling)
Do you have difficulty walking?
(Joking)
- Walking is tough for me. - What's wrong with you?
My legs aren't flexible.
Stretch your back too.
He even circles his hips oddly.
You remind me of a newborn elk.
(Utterly ashamed)
I'm just not flexible.
- You're really inflexible. - I am.
- You're a log. - Yes, I'm a log.
- You can't circle your hips at all. - This isn't important...
when playing tennis.
- I can hit it right away. - Isn't this samba?
- You're criticizing him a lot. - Yes.
My gosh, you're so inflexible.
His service will tell us everything.
- My gosh. - That was swift.
- My gosh. What? - Oh, my.
- Ju Seung is good. - What was that?
(Startled)
(Flinging it down)
- That's... - I wanted to make him laugh.
- It was like... - Hey.
swatting away a mosquito or a bee.
- But you can't do that. - Gosh, this is making me mad.
(He serves again.)
(Coach Ju Seung takes care of it with ease.)
(Falling)
What do I do when it's too low?
Then you must lower your body like this.
- Lower my body? - I see.
Or you must change to a backhand grip and hit it.
As for Hyun Moo,
the color of his face has been off.
He seemed to be losing energy lately.
His face was sagging too.
He doesn't have energy these days.
I thought that learning badminton...
would hopefully make his body flexible.
He must train a lot to improve.
So I kept trying to push him to hit the shuttlecock.
- He sounds like a coach. - He's talking like a coach.
- Like a coach. - Like a coach for a national team.
- He thinks Hyun Moo is... - Yes.
- three levels beneath him. - Right.
He's talking about Hyun Moo like Hyun Moo is his junior.
Hey, let's make a wager.
- Let's play for ten points. - What?
- A wager? - The loser buys lunch.
The loser buys lunch? Okay.
Okay. I got it. Nice.
(The game to score 10 points begins.)
I can manage a basic serve. Yes.
That's a nice sound.
(They trade shots with utter intensity.)
(It lands inside the court.)
- Darn it. - It's 1 to 0.
- My gosh, yes. - Oh, my.
Ju Seung is good.
Nice.
(Did you see that, Hyun Moo?)
I got a point.
- Give me the shuttlecock. - That was a nasty shot.
(Ju Seung: 1, Hyun Moo: 0)
You must know how to disguise shots whether they're long or short.
(Zooming by)
That was sneaky.
- There. - Don't you think that was sneaky?
- Gosh. - Right.
- The mind game is important. - You're good.
It's important to figure out if it will be a long or short shot.
Beginners can't hit back a long shot.
We can't.
(It's Ju Seung's service again.)
(Moomoo loses another point.)
You're trying to score points with your service.
We can go on since you can't hit back my serve.
He sounds so annoying.
- Ju Seung is easily winning. - Right.
Hey, he's so good.
You should switch to the backhand grip.
Keep your left foot in the front.
Step forward with your right foot and hit it like this.
If it's a short shot, this is what you do.
I did that, so I could teach him everything he needed to know.
Then... Here.
- That was good. - Nice.
(He manages to hit the shuttlecock with the backhand grip.)
(Smacking)
That must hurt.
(It hits his nipple.)
He somehow got the third eye.
He aimed the third eye on the right.
- It must've pushed in your nipple. - Yes.
One of my eyes went blind because of him.
Then did you play with your third eye closed?
- I had to play like this. - Like this?
This is my main eye.
- You were at a disadvantage. - I see.
(A penalty on his eyesight)
He's smiling from ear to ear.
That's Ju Seung's biggest smile I've seen so far.
Seriously. You seem so happy.
I was elated.
It hurts my pride even to be compared to him.
So we're in different worlds, in terms of quantum mechanics.
Can you fathom my level now?
(Smacking his lips)
(He's been scolded by Hyun Moo in the past.)
(Texting with Ju Seung is so boring.)
(Happy birthday, Hyun Moo. Stay healthy and happy as always.)
(His message was so dull.)
Even a message from the AI won't sound that boring.
(Has he gone mad?)
(Utterly criticized)
This is Ju Seung's revenge.
Gosh. Ju Seung trained...
for four months for his revenge?
He also had to consider the time to hook Hyun Moo.
- Right. - If we're counting all that,
- it took about 4 years. - It took 4 years.
- It took four years. - He was working toward that.
- Just for one day. - That's it.
Okay.
Yes, get your revenge.
(Okay, come at me!)
- What's that? - Why is he raising his racket?
I'm playing with your head.
- Like the praying mantis. - Right.
It's like a peacock spreading its feathers.
- He looks like a blue crab too. - Right, the blue crabs.
- You're like a frilled-neck lizard. - Right.
(Try all you want, but it won't work on me.)
That's it.
- Show us. - Great.
(He finally has a revenge match after 4 years.)
- Nice. - What's going on?
(Hitting)
Okay.
- You're warmed up now. - You're warmed up.
(Moomoo desperately fights back to Ju Seung.)
(I can't lose out to Ju Seung of all people.)
(He finally has a chance to take his revenge on Hyun Moo.)
That's it.
- Show us. - Great.
(He finally has a revenge match after 4 years.)
- Nice. - What's going on?
(Hitting)
Okay.
- You're warmed up now. - You're warmed up.
(Moomoo desperately fights back to Ju Seung.)
(I can't lose out to Ju Seung of all people.)
My goodness.
- That's in. - What just happened?
(His powerful smash shot lands inside the court.)
That's in.
(Did you see that?)
(He finally shows a smile of victory.)
(Adoring Hyun Moo)
It took four years to prepare for this.
Are you going to wait until the next Summer Games?
- Right now... - The next Summer Games?
It seems whoever serves ends up winning a point.
So both of us are beginners.
(Service is all about the energy.)
I'll show it to you now.
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
- Great. - That was sneaky.
He keeps calling Ju Seung sneaky whenever he wins a point.
Seriously. You're so sneaky.
You don't even think about moving your feet.
But you must.
- It's out. - Darn it.
- It's the match point. - The match point.
(In no time, it's a match point.)
(With one more point, my revenge is over.)
- Great. - His body seems light.
I haven't seen him run at all.
Nice.
(A powerful shot)
(Floundering)
Okay. It's over. Yes!
(Ju Seung wins the game with a new side of him.)
Nicely done.
- Did you feel the level difference? - No.
You see, this is the gap between our levels.
Is that the better side?
- The court? - Let's switch.
- This side is better. - He's blaming it on the court.
- I see. It's not over yet. - This side is narrower.
They'll play one more round of this?
Forget about everything then. Let's change the shuttlecock.
Let's play for five points and be done with it.
- For 5 points? - That's as good as 100 points.
- They'll play for five points. - Okay.
You can be sneaky or do whatever you want.
(You just wait, Lee Ju Seung.)
(Hyun Moo, you can't beat me.)
(It begins with Hyun Moo's service.)
- It's out. - Why?
(Is this out?)
- He doesn't know the rules yet. - It's out.
- Why? - What's that?
- It must end up in that box. - It must go diagonally.
Really?
There's no such rule like that.
Let's just play.
- But we must follow the rules. - What?
- Okay. Fine. - Who serves like this?
Okay. I didn't know. It's 0 to 0.
Seriously? "I didn't know."
Let's follow the rules.
It's okay to be sneaky too.
(Hyun Moo ambushes him with the service.)
- Gosh, he hit it back. - He hit it back.
- Okay. - Let's keep playing.
My gosh.
- It's out. Okay. - No.
- No. - Why is that out?
No.
- It hit the ceiling. - Okay.
- No. - No.
- No. - It will be out next time.
- You said it was okay to be sneaky. - Okay.
- This won't count. - My gosh. This...
(It won't count.)
My gosh. This...
(Another ambush)
- Okay. - It's out.
- It's in. - It's in.
It's in. Come on.
Come on. It landed in the court. Seriously.
- It's 1 to 0. - That was a practice run.
(A practice run)
- Seriously. - When will the game begin?
- What is this? - What's the point?
- When will it begin? - My gosh.
- You'll play until you win. - That's not it.
- I didn't know the rules. - My gosh.
- He keeps saying it doesn't count. - What is this?
- You're so stubborn. - My gosh.
I like that he's shamelessly brazen.
I haven't heard that...
- since elementary school. - Right.
I've never seen anyone who had no sense of sportsmanship.
- You're just arguing. - Right.
- Gosh. - What are they doing then?
- We'll play for real. - For real.
- Don't goof around. Here it goes. - For real.
Here it is at last.
(It's Hyun Moo's service again.)
- It's out. - What do you mean?
- It hit here. - You didn't tell me about that.
- What? - I didn't know.
(Dumbfounded)
- Seriously. - Listen.
- Oh, my. - I didn't know.
- What is this? - Right.
- I bet it was tough for Ju Seung. - Seriously.
Hey, even I think I'm the worst.
- It must land in the box. - Your serve must land here.
- Your serve... - You should've told me that before.
- Your serve must land here. - Where?
Inside the box, right?
(He serves again after the explanation.)
- It's out. - It's in.
- It's out. - Why?
(It's out.)
- It's a fault. - Your serve must land in the box.
I didn't know.
Just leave the court and grab a meal.
- Just go and eat. - Why are you playing this?
- What's the point of this game? - My gosh.
- I didn't want to buy him a meal. - Come on. Why not?
No one would be this unreasonable even for rock-paper-scissors.
He kept teasing me.
Or you could have gotten a meal separately.
- That's an option too. - Yes.
- Hear me out. - You should've known this.
- Who serves... - How would I know?
I've taken only one class so far.
Service must land in the small box.
That was so draining.
Yes.
(Their rally is getting lengthy.)
- You got it. - Nice.
- Nice. - My gosh.
Good job.
- Nice. - Oh, no!
(A powerful smash shot to end the rally)
Oh, no.
(Right on the bullseye)
- Why did you keep bullying him? - Oh, no.
It hit me on my you-know-what.
Nice.
It's not nice.
- Seriously. - No, I meant...
- no excuses. - This was humiliating.
This feels so insulting.
(Laughing)
(His anger level is rising.)
(You just wait.)
(It begins with Ju Seung's service.)
- It's in. - Out.
(It drops in the court after hitting the wall.)
It's out.
- It's in. - Out.
(It's in.)
- It's in. - It's out.
- What is this? - It's in.
He kept insisting that it was in.
(Hyun Moo insists that it's in.)
It's in.
He's trying to be patient, not a patient.
- Right, he's trying to be patient. - Right, patient.
- He's got no decency. - It's in.
It's in.
(He says it's in as soon as he serves.)
How can you say that...
even before it hits the court?
- It landed here. - Okay.
Service is difficult.
(Serving gently)
Okay. I explained this to you earlier.
- It must cross this line. - I forgot.
(I forgot.)
It must cross this line.
My goodness.
- Then... - My gosh.
- This is getting interesting. - Yes, it is.
- I forgot. - I can't wait to hear his excuse.
- At this rate, he'll be invincible. - My gosh.
- I didn't see that coming. - Gosh.
I'll end it.
(I'll end this now.)
(Looking determined)
(It goes back and forth in a sharp rally.)
- Nice. - That's good.
Nice.
- Nice. - Keep playing to the end.
- I hit it back. - He hit it up.
- He hit it up. - That's instant agility.
- That's An Se Young. - My gosh.
- That's amazing. - I'm Moo Se Young.
- Moo Se Young. - Nice.
- Nice. - It's the An Se Young move.
Nice.
- You couldn't hit it back? - It's the An Se Young move.
- How could he hit it back? - The An Se Young move. It's over.
(Hyun Moo wins.)
(After winning the match,)
(An Se Young opened up her arms to celebrate.)
- Shuttlecock Prince Moo Se Young. - The An Se Young move. It's over.
- You lost in the end? - You lost?
He did.
It's over.
It was a good game.
By the way, my last shot was pretty cool, right?
I'll tell everyone that I won.
Are you tired?
I heard you were in good shape.
You didn't move around.
But I did.
But I still won.
Imagine what would happen if I moved around.
(Feeling miserable)
You'd be in big trouble.
That was a good game.
I heard you could play for hours.
Why are you so weak?
It's not that I'm weak.
You drained my energy because you kept insisting it was in.
You said that even before it hit the floor.
To be fair,
- the victory should go to him. - Yes.
Actually, I was shocked...
- after playing that game. - Yes.
I made a promise to my instructor that I'd train at least once a week.
- When I'm somewhat ready, - You'll train?
- I'll challenge you formally. - Another one?
- Great. - Really?
- I mean it. - "I forgot."
You should play doubles at a competition.
I want us to play doubles together.
- You want to compete? - Yes.
- There's one for beginners. - Yes.
It will be just beginners at the competition.
- There's one for beginners. Yes. - Yes. For beginners.
Hey, we played for two hours.
- It was a good workout. - You played hard.
Badminton can help you lose weight.
I've been training here for four months now.
This was the most draining session.
You didn't go over what would be considered in.
- It must cross this line. - I forgot.
I keep hearing his voice saying, "It's in."
You're so out of it.
Hey. I know that I barely moved around.
But since it's fun, it's a good workout.
(I see.)
After playing badminton, I saw the need to keep at it.
It makes you lose fat fast.
- That's right. - This?
You're sweating so much after playing with me.
- Look at the sweat on your neck. - He's flushing now.
It's an intense cardio workout.
- Of course. - It's really intense.
- It's an intense cardio workout. - It must be.
We must have a referee next time we play together.
You keep forgetting the rules.
(Embarrassed)
Did you drink something?
I did.
(Gulping down)
It must be refreshing after working out.
It's good to drink it.
- Gosh, it's so refreshing. - It was really refreshing.
It's making up for the sweat I lost.
I used to play badminton a lot.
It's Sunday, and it's not even 9am yet.
Exactly. Why did you call me so early in the morning?
I wanted to make the day long.
- At 9am? - Yes. Let's go eat.
- You want to eat when it's 9am? - Yes.
It's been a while for me too.
- It's breakfast for you. - Of course.
It wasn't even brunch. It was breakfast.
- Yes, it's breakfast. - I bet no place is open.
Where should we eat?
There's udon, soba, and...
How about hand-cut kalguksu?
That's a good place.
It's where I go often.
- Why didn't you tell me? - I've been going there since young.
- But at this hour... - You've been going there...
since young, but why did I look up that place?
I mean...
Because it opens at 11:30am.
- Let's eat there later. - Sure.
Are you willing to work out more?
- Work out? - Yes.
I'm not tired yet, so...
Then let's not drive to the restaurant.
Let's get there by slow jogging.
- What is that? - What is slow jogging?
I hear that's trending these days.
So many people recommended it to me.
- Slow jogging? - Yes.
More people have been recommending slow jogging than running to me.
I heard it was really good.
- I've never heard of slow jogging. - I thought, "Let's go jogging."
I've never heard of such things, but he always says they're trending.
You don't know what it is?
It's not fast walking?
It's different from race walking?
It's jogging slowly, strictly speaking.
- That is running. - That's...
When you run, you control your pace...
- by going slow and then fast. - You control your pace as you run.
I'm not talking about going that slow.
- Oh, is that so? - See how slow I jog.
- Then that's walking. - That's walking.
No, it's not.
- What do you mean? - You'll realize it when you see it.
I could tolerate Yin-Yang Water.
- Right. That was too much. - Stop making things up anymore.
It's something in between...
- walking and running. - I mean...
- Really? - Hashtag, slow jogging. Look it up.
I've never seen such hashtags.
- I've never seen it either. - Just take a look.
I saw the video of slow jogging, and it didn't look that hard.
- Look at that. - That's running.
I guess it's a new type.
Seongsu-dong isn't that far from Gangnam.
It's around 3km to 4km.
Running a few kilometers itself...
was a challenge for me.
Let's run to Seongsu-dong, then.
- Slow jogging? - Yes, slow jogging.
It's trending these days.
It's my 1st time hearing it in the 42 years of my life.
So you don't look up hashtags.
- Do you only do things that trend? - Yes. I don't do it if it's old.
- Is this how you do it? - Go like this.
Make sure the ball of your foot touches the ground first.
This is running.
What happens if you run?
It impacts your knees.
But if you let the ball of your foot touch the ground first,
- your joints are less strained. - Oh, the ball of your foot?
You're right. The ball of your foot...
- absorbs the shock. - Right?
And you keep moving your body too.
- Your whole body. - If you feel like you can run fast,
- can you? - No, you'll be told off...
because it strains your joints.
This is what they call slow jogging.
- Did you learn it? - No, I watched a video about it.
People kept saying that it's trending these days.
It must raise my heart rate a bit.
Of course.
Did you quit warping?
I haven't been doing it because of my knees.
We could apply warping in slow jogging.
Like this.
This is much harder, right?
I think warping is slower than slow jogging.
I bet if we use warping,
we'll get there in 15 minutes.
That'd be as fast as a car.
(Giggling)
Keep your arms at a 90-degree angle.
(A miracle morning on an empty street to strengthen your immunity)
You need to use your whole body.
If there's a red light,
- should we jog in place? - We should.
If you stop, everything will be in vain.
You need to keep jogging. You shouldn't stop.
- You can't stop. Keep going. - What if you need to pee?
- You should pee as you jog. - Pee as you jog?
(You should pee as you jog.)
- You need to dry it as you jog. - That's slow jogging?
You must be jogging even in the restroom.
- Really? Even in the restroom? - Yes.
You'll be told off by the cleaning people.
Then do you have to keep jogging as you're being told off?
You should with your hands behind your back.
"I'm sorry. It's my fault."
- "It's splattering all over." - "Sorry."
"I'll wipe that later."
It is clearly different from running.
- Now I finally get it. - It doesn't give you time to rest.
It is really different.
(They've been running in place for a while, waiting for the green light.)
Ju Seung is doing his best to follow him.
All right.
I can't believe we're running on this street.
I always drive past here.
- It must be tiring, though. - It is.
It makes you sweat a lot.
It is definitely less straining on your joints.
Are your joints in bad shape now?
They're in good shape.
Running on asphalt is really bad for your joints.
(As they take care of their joint health...)
It's Yeongdong Bridge.
(They're on Yeongdong Bridge in no time.)
Do you know a song called "Yeongdong Bridge in the Rain?"
No.
(On Yeongdong Bridge on a rainy night)
(Walking there by myself)
- You don't know the song? - You said you were TSM.
("Yeongdong Bridge in the Rain" by Joo Hyun Mi)
Jennie could do a remake of the song.
Trot Sensitive Man, not Trend Sensitive Man.
Isn't that a song from my grandma's time?
- I think I've heard of it. - You're acting like you're an MZ.
You guys look like healthy father and son.
Right. They look like...
- father and son. - Exactly.
It's good to see you two running together.
(Running on Yeongdong Bridge with the dad's youth)
I watched the merits of slow jogging...
on "Mysteries of the Human Body."
The case subjects weren't much different from me.
As in their lifestyles or their body conditions.
("Gwangju's Seo-gu Opens the Era of Living Healthy with Slow Jogging")
(Stop worrying about your joints!)
(People of all generations enjoy slow jogging.)
Maybe it was developed for the elderly.
A dad's challenge.
A dad's challenge?
Hang in there, Dad.
- You really kept going. - We never stopped.
I only said that because it made sense.
- Look at Ju Seung. - He stopped.
- That's what he did. - He stopped.
- We need to keep jogging. - We need to press this.
Don't use that as an excuse.
What time is it?
We need to run in place while waiting for the green light.
- Your arms. There you go. - He's getting tired.
He's so sweet, though. He's jogging for Hyun Moo.
He's a good son.
(Their joint immunity has strengthened to the fullest.)
This is a popular spot on weekends.
Seongsu-dong on weekends is really busy.
What is this?
- What? It must be a popup store. - They must be lining up.
(The popular place among MZers is crowded since morning.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Thank you.
- Hello. - Yes, I'll complete the race.
This must be how Kian84 feels.
(Enjoying the young energy among the MZers)
Ju Seung is running in a cool way all of a sudden.
He's so self-conscious.
Wait a minute.
He was making a fool of himself because he was self-conscious.
(Super immersed)
Look how he's acting so cool.
Hello.
(That's right. I'm the Healthy Seongsu Man.)
(Smiling)
- Things have changed a lot here. - Gosh, the smell of bread.
What is this? It's salt bread, isn't it?
It smells like salt bread.
- It smells like salt bread. - Where? Salt bread?
- I heard it's famous. - It is.
There's one in Apgujeong-dong too.
- Gosh, the smell of bread. - Gosh.
- Shall we have one? - Yes, we should.
- Is this the line? - This is the line for payment.
You live around here. You've never been here before?
I'm not familiar with South Seongsu-dong.
- Who calls it South Seongsu-dong? - I...
What is South Seongsu-dong?
- What is South Seongsu-Dong? - He lives in the northern part,
so he calls it South Seongsu-dong.
- What on earth does that mean? - From Seongsu Station,
the southern part is South Seongsu-dong.
- My house is in North Seongsu-dong. - It's my first time...
hearing anyone call it South Seongsu-dong.
He lives in Seongsu-dong too, but he doesn't know about it at all.
- I didn't know. - Actually, I came up with it.
- South Seongsu-dong. - It's my standard.
No one uses such terms.
(Should I use them?)
South Seongsu-dong.
I don't come here often because it's crowded.
You're so handsome!
You're a good liar.
(You're a good liar.)
(Jogging in line)
Salt bread? What are you doing?
They're jogging without stopping.
(Slow jogging in place)
This looks really weird.
It looks like a game that's crashed.
Like an NPC.
- That's right. - Like the ones in "GTA."
- You're right. It's like that. - "GTA."
"Will you buy bread?"
(Quest: Do not stop slow jogging.)
(Will you stand in front of the self-service kiosk?)
Next customer. Please order from here.
- Did you see that? - Like "GTA."
- You stopped. Come on. - No, you stopped. Come on.
- You should've kept jogging. - I apologize.
- Oh, we have to order 4. - It's 4, no matter what.
I should've kept jogging. What was I doing?
I must've been crazy.
It's because of the self-service kiosk.
I lost my pace.
(He starts jogging again.)
(Among many people who are in line,)
(they persistently keep slow jogging.)
(One-two)
That looks good.
- Come on. - Thank you.
- I lost it at the smell. - Thank you.
You lost control.
(He stops jogging at the thought of having bread.)
Come here. Let's eat this.
It's our first meal of the day.
They're not thinking of jogging at all.
- Because we'd lose the salt. - They lost control.
(Freshly baked salt bread)
It's warm.
Smell it. How is it?
(Smelling the bread first)
It's like... It smells like bread from abroad.
It smells buttery, right?
It must be good.
Freshly baked bread is so good.
(Sticking it close to his nose)
It's good!
(A grain of salt on his nose)
There's just enough amount of salt.
It was really good...
- to have it after running. - I want to have salt bread.
It's so savory.
I'll give the rest to you as a gift. Keep it in the fridge.
Thank you.
It's so good.
It's funny how he's acting like he's doing a big favor...
by offering the bread as a gift.
(Embarrassed)
(Wiping his mouth with tissue)
(Glancing)
- Why put the trash in his backpack? - Goodness.
(What was that?)
You know...
I can't litter.
- That was so natural, though. - "Love for the environment?"
He threw it in my backpack naturally.
Let's run.
He's indeed an actor.
Look at that. He doesn't run when he eats.
(Fully motivated to run after eating)
Shall we have kalguksu?
That's where we're going.
- We are, right? - Yes.
They look like they need to go to the bathroom.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Is it far? - We're almost there.
- We are? - Yes.
We're almost there.
They walked for quite a lot.
Goodness, they went far.
We're here.
You've been saying that for 150 times now.
Over here.
- Bossam. - Oh, okay.
It's a bossam and kalguksu place.
I went to elementary school in Seongsu-dong.
It's the restaurant I've been going since elementary school.
It's a really old popular restaurant in Seongsu-dong.
Hyun Moo's immunity is low right now,
so I wanted to feed him pork, which is good for your immunity.
That's why I brought him to a bossam place.
If he enjoyed the meal even from then,
- Then it's a real deal. - that means it's a good place.
He must've had it with his parents...
when he was young.
I trusted his parents' palate, actually.
(Bitter)
Is it...
We open at 11:30am.
Oh, at 11:30am?
- Oh, there's a line. - They're waiting.
- Gosh, this place is incredible. - So there's a line.
- They're waiting. Look. - Hello.
- Look. There's a line there too. - Gosh.
- Goodness. - Are you filming?
(They plop down while waiting.)
We look so shabby.
Goodness.
- It was tiring. - Great job.
But you still went there.
- Yes, we did. - You made it.
It was quite far.
Have some jelly.
- They're going in. - They're going in.
Great.
(Getting more energy at the thought of eating)
Ma'am, the bossam set has kalguksu too, right?
- Yes. - The bossam set.
- Okay. - We'll have two bossam sets.
The tables are full.
- Look at that. - It's full?
The tables became full as soon as they opened.
(Ju Seung's favorite Seongsu place got filled as soon as it opened.)
(Approaching)
So this is...
(Bossam filled with protein that will strengthen your immunity)
- This is crazy. - That looks really good.
- It's so glossy. - It's filled with protein.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
- He eats so well. - It's delicious.
That's like an open sandwich.
(Pushing it in in one bite)
There you go.
(Eye-opening)
How are his eyes so big?
Like Heartsping.
(Because he's Shih-Tzu-ping.)
- Do you approve of it? - It's the best.
I like having it with rice.
Of course. It's good.
(Opening wide)
(Shih-Tzu-ping is in love with the taste of the meat.)
(He continues inhaling it.)
(Savoring)
It tastes even better when you eat it after working out.
It's a perfect meal after working out.
Gosh, the seasoning looks good. It smells nice.
(He quickly tries the soup while it's hot.)
- The seasoning is... Gosh. - He's adding pepper.
(Adding lots of pepper after a bite)
Aren't you adding too much?
That's like pepper soup.
(Sneezing)
I'm sorry.
Gosh, the pepper...
(How can you eat that?)
Look. The pepper is all gone.
That's because it all settled at the bottom of the bowl.
It's mixed with noodles and soup.
(Let me try it.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, this place is good.
(Exclaiming)
The soup.
(I must have the soup.)
I'm going to have kalguksu tomorrow, no matter what.
You can never get bored of kalguksu.
(Slurping)
(This is it. It's thrilling.)
Hey.
The kalguksu is so good.
(Tasty invigorating food)
(Inhaling it in earnest)
(To recover lost health)
He eats so well.
(As he eats passionately,)
(his immune cells start running again.)
(Refreshed)
He looks healthy.
I feel like my stomach is going to explode.
It was rewarding.
Having the soup made with beef broth on an empty stomach...
after working out...
(Inhaling beef broth)
The nutrients seeped into the bones and cells.
I felt so proud of myself.
It felt like everything I had became nutrients for my body.
- Ju Seung, thank you. - Yes.
I'm more grateful for this than when you took me to the hospital.
For telling me about this place.
I'm so full.
Your blood sugar spiked.
Yes, it did.
- Can I take a nap at your place? - Sorry?
Can I take a nap at your place that looks like the Severance Hospital?
Yes, you can.
- Can I sleep there? - Yes.
- I'll pay for this. - Thank you for the meal.
(Laughing)
- You jog well now. - It's like we're filming...
It's like we're filming a short film.
You're running again?
- You jog well now. - I walk again today.
I think I've gotten...
used to it.
I'm so used to it that I feel like...
- I'd walk like this every day. - I know.
I don't think I can jog alone like this.
Jogging alone like this could be a little hard.
Even with a mask on.
Your side must hurt since you're running after eating.
That much is okay.
Why did it get cold all of a sudden?
That's because we're in North Seongsu-dong.
This place is a bit like "Rustic Period."
Is North Seongsu-dong cold?
- Since it's north. - I see.
You have immense pride in North Seongsu-dong.
North Seongsu-dong is the real Seongsu-dong.
South Seongsu-dong is like...
"Spirited Away."
What does that mean?
It's around here.
Where do you live?
(After a meaningful immunity-strengthening course)
Gosh, I finally got to come here.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
I've never visited Ju Seung's new house.
(Gosh, it's Ju Seung's house.)
I get to see the unidentifiable lighting in person.
You put up my picture right here.
- It gave off a good vibe. - Thanks.
I told you to remove the lighting next to the stove,
but it's still there.
(The red lighting that gave off red smoke at an odd spot)
I thought your rice cooker was on fire.
- It gives off sunset lighting. - Sunset?
That's the sunset, and this is...
This is my oasis.
And there's an octopus guarding over it.
An octopus is guarding over it?
- And if you look here... - The Severance Hospital?
It really looks like a hospital ward.
The Severance Hospital.
I changed the layout.
- You kept calling it a hospital. - You did.
I moved the bed to this side.
I wanted to make it look more spacious.
(He moved the bed to make use of the space.)
It looks more like a hospital now.
- The blanket you got last time. - Yes.
A deep green blanket. It helps me sleep really well.
It looks like a VIP ward.
(Fascinated)
It gets plenty of light too.
Gosh, it's like an old blind from a countryside hospital.
I bought it recently, though.
Your house is really nice.
Well, I...
When you move to a new place,
a guest needs to do it...
Do what?
- Go number two. - I see.
Is there such a belief?
I've heard of it too, but...
Then you should take a dump at my place too.
I'll do it for you anytime.
I'll wash my feet too, since I'm at your place.
Sure. Wash your feet too.
- Use whatever towel you want. - Okay.
(He goes to the bathroom to relieve himself.)
(Splash)
- It was that loud? - I think it was louder than that.
(Working hard while Hyun Moo is pooping)
What is that?
I made it. Give it a try.
It's a healthy drink with amino acids.
(Giving a drink with amino acids to strengthen his immunity)
I feel like I got closer to you to have come to your place casually.
I know. You should come to Seongsu more often.
You get closer to someone when you visit their house.
I rarely go out except when I go to...
the Korean meal buffet or gym.
Is your gym nearby?
The gym is at the end of North Seongsu-dong.
Can you stop calling it North Seongsu-dong? It's so...
It's how I divide the area.
Based on Seongsu Station,
the southern part is...
(What?)
By the way, it smells a lot.
(Getting up)
What smell?
The smell from the bathroom.
Goodness.
(Shutting the door while holding his breath)
- It smelled? - It smelled a little.
It smelled stale.
You're attacking me like this?
(It just smelled bad.)
Let's turn on the candle.
I'm going to take a nap.
- You can. - I'm so tired.
I had to wash my blankets anyway.
So I'll wash the blankets after you take a nap.
You want me to sleep in the dirty blankets?
No, I meant that you could sleep comfortably.
Sure. Where will you sleep?
At my oasis. You can sleep there.
We're not sleeping together?
What are they doing?
It's too small.
You've slept with me there before.
- During our temple stay. - Oh, the temple stay?
You should sleep alone today since the bed is too small.
Let's take a nap.
Take a nap. I'm so tired.
Do you want to wash first?
Are you going to wash?
You said you wanted to sleep.
(You said you wanted to sleep.)
- What kind of talk is this? - Gosh!
- You need to wash before sleeping. - Wash if you want to or not!
Goodness.
(What are you talking about, Hyun Moo?)
What are you saying?
Let's sleep together.
I'll sleep here.
- Why? - You can sleep there.
Do you find me difficult?
"Do you find me difficult?" What kind of question is that?
It's not that. The bed is too small.
Do you want to try lying on it together?
Yes.
Come here.
My gosh. It's hilarious.
- It's a super single. - Yes, it's...
big enough for two men.
- This? - It's too small.
Yes, it's really spacious.
Even Ku Sung Hwan can lie on it too.
Goodness. Two men on a super single? It must be too hard.
It's not hard at all.
I've slept with Jang Woo before too.
This is so nice.
Isn't it really nice?
(Isn't it really nice?)
(What's wrong with him?)
It's quite nice.
(Giggling)
He sounds like a kettle.
(He laughs like a whistling kettle.)
(Happy)
It's quite nice.
- It'll bring us closer. - It's nice, Hyun Moo.
- Yes. - I love that you're sleeping over.
Why are you putting up a wall?
No. It's just that there's a lot of space.
Why?
(He sticks to the younger member who's putting up a wall.)
- I hate it so much. - My goodness.
(Why are they behaving that way?)
(Happy)
(Hyun Moo and Ju Seung get ready to sleep in the same bed.)
This place makes me drowsy.
The bed and all.
That warmth would anger me.
Seriously.
(Exhaling)
Your breath...
The sound of your breath gets on my nerves.
I hated the sound of his breath.
- I can't do this. - What?
- I'll sleep on the sofa. - Why?
- The sound of your breath... - What are you doing?
(He escapes the deep green bed.)
- What are you doing? - I wanted to turn off the light.
- I wanted to turn off the light. - Okay.
(Staring intently)
(Laughing)
- What? - Well,
I hate it when you look at me from the bed.
(I hate it when you look at me from the bed.)
It was so entertaining to see him suffer.
He has the best reactions.
- Hurry up and lie down. - Okay.
(Tapping)
You know...
(He goes back to the bed.)
I'm sensitive to heat, so I'll lie on top of the duvet.
I'm sensitive to heat as well.
(Lifting the duvet)
(Hot)
(Two men who are sensitive to heat lie on top of the duvet.)
What's this?
(Let's sleep.)
(They fall asleep peacefully.)
It has been a while.
What? Is he sleep-talking?
It has been a while...
since I lay next to someone.
(It has been a while since I lay next to someone.)
- You know what I mean, right? - It's scary.
(Glancing over)
(Shuddering)
(Screaming)
Stop it.
I wanted to torment him until the end.
Your leg hair is like a steel scrubber...
for the restroom.
It's velvet.
- Velvet. - Velvet.
(They speak nonsense.)
Let's take a nap for an hour.
Then we can jog and go out for dinner.
Ju Seung's immune system will suffer.
(I Live Alone)
(Just Like the First Time)
(Jae Hyeon is going somewhere quickly.)
The weather is nice.
(Glancing over)
- There's a cow's head. - Where is he at?
- A cow's head. - It's a market.
(Majang Meat Market)
Majang-dong.
- It's a nice place. - It's fun.
It was my first visit.
To give a gift to people...
who are dear to me,
I visited the Mecca of beef, Majang-dong.
- You should eat it yourself. - Seriously.
Don't think about giving it as a gift.
It's the best place for meat.
- It's huge. - That's right.
I was very surprised.
(Korean beef)
- There's nine. - It has been a while.
He should eat it.
(There's well-marbled meat.)
You can find the best meat in Majang-dong.
That's right.
It's so fresh. Look at those cow trotters.
(Looking around)
(Fascinated)
There are so many shops.
It looks delicious.
- The level of enthusiasm... - He needs to eat some beef.
is definitely different.
- It's different. - Na Rae, Hyun Moo, and Jang Woo...
can't go past three blocks.
People stop us at the entrance.
They can't walk around in there.
(The Palm Oil Family is insanely popular at the markets.)
Na Rae.
(They have a big appetite.)
They'll escort the Palm Oil Family.
"Please come here."
Really?
They'll bring us beef tartare before we go past two blocks.
"Gosh, Hyun Moo."
- "Na Rae." - Totally.
- They'll dip it in sauce. - Yes.
- "Na Rae." - That's right.
I should've known. I don't look like a big eater.
Majang-dong doesn't like that kind of a body type.
You're right. No one is rushing over.
He's unwelcomed.
(The man with the unpopular body walks amidst disinterest.)
There are so many shops.
- Hello. Welcome. - Hello.
- Sir, I... - What are you looking for?
I want to buy some beef.
Is it a gift or for yourself?
I need both a gift and something for myself.
- Shall I take a look? - Please look at the menu inside.
- Please go inside. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
What's this cut?
It's top sirloin.
- Top sirloin? - Yes.
How is it so well-marbled?
- It looks like 2 plus. - The grade must be 9.
- Top sirloin. - It looks so tasty.
- The grade must be nine. - Top sirloin,
- rib finger, - Okay.
and chuck flap tail.
- I want to give a gift. - Okay.
How much should I get? Which cuts should I get?
You should get an assortment of ribeye, rib finger,
chuck flap tail, ribeye cap,
- and thin skirt. - All right.
- Then there'll be some fatty cuts. - Yes.
- Both fatty cuts and lean cuts. - I see.
Why do you keep rubbing your hands like a fly?
- I don't know what to do. - Seriously.
- Don't do this. Be confident. - You'll fly off at that rate.
- I mean... - He wants a lot.
He's scared that they won't sell him meat.
"I'll eat a lot, so please sell me some meat."
"Please don't neglect me."
"Please give me more."
(Staring)
- Which cut is that? - It's ribeye cap.
(Which cut is that?)
- Yes. - It's curled up like a shrimp.
That's where it gets its nickname.
- It looks like a shrimp. - Ribeye cap is tasty.
- It's shaped like a shrimp. - Yes.
- This cut is thin skirt. - Yes.
The meat is so high-quality that I can't tell the cuts apart.
- They look similar, right? - Yes.
- This cut is chuck flap tail. - Look at that.
- The fat looks like snow. - It's like tuna.
- This cut is neck chain. - It's tasty.
- Yes, it's tasty. - Neck chain.
- It's chewy... - Yes.
and lean.
(Fancy)
- You bought a lot. - My goodness.
- Doesn't it look nice? - It's so nice.
My mouth is watering.
- That's how it gets packed. - Yes.
We put a sticker on it.
You packaged it well.
- It looks tasty. - They make it look luxurious.
They'll love it.
(Rummaging)
I want the gold-colored cloth.
- Yes. This one is nice. - This one?
- It should be wrapped. - Okay.
It's the color of 23K gold. I like this color.
- The package is quite big. - Yes.
These people must be special to receive a gift like this.
They're very special.
Is it his teacher?
Someone who's very precious.
- May I use this card? - Yes.
- Here you go. Thank you. - Okay.
- I'll enjoy it. - Please enjoy it.
- It'll be a good gift. Thank you. - Thank you.
I hope it'll be a good gift.
(He puts the precious gift safely in the trunk.)
He still drives a small car.
(Let's hurry up and go.)
It's hot. It's getting hot.
- It's the deficiency heat. - That's what it is.
It's still cold.
(He drives for a while...)
(and reaches Goyang.)
- Goyang. - He went far.
(My goodness)
(Laughing)
You've reached your destination.
It feels like the countryside.
- My goodness. - It's a hanok house.
- It's so pretty. - It's nice, right?
- It's so nice. - What is that place?
(What is that hanok house?)
(He gets out of the car.)
Ma'am, hello.
Jae Hyeon, welcome.
It's good to see you.
- Jae Hyeon, welcome. - My goodness.
Your face hasn't changed at all.
You became a star.
- I don't think they're his parents. - Who are they?
Sir, hello.
- Jae Hyeon. - Sir, hello.
Are you in good health?
Jae Hyeon is the skinniest.
He's the skinniest.
They're the parents of Park Jae Kang, my alumnus...
from elementary school to high school.
They're your friend's parents.
They look so nice.
We became close in fourth grade.
As for the second friend, An Hyung Jin,
we became close in middle school.
They're my best friends who have been with me...
since my teenage years.
- They're his best friends. - My goodness.
(Jae Hyeon, Jae Kang, Hyung Jin)
They look mischievous.
I've known them for over 20 years.
(They've known each other for over 20 years.)
The three of us continue to be friends.
(They're more than best friends.)
Are all of your friends married?
They have children.
- Both of them? - Both of them have children.
Both of them have two sons.
- I see. - I see.
Hyun Jin's children are twins.
You're well-mannered.
You greeted the parents...
- before the friends. - Of course.
- I... - Who wouldn't do that?
Who would ignore the parents?
"Ma'am, you're in my way. Hey."
"I'll greet you later."
"Why do you keep talking to me?"
I've never seen anyone do that.
He was happy to see his friends.
When I was little, I often came here for sleepovers.
- I often stayed overnight. - Really?
Jae Kang's father made a tasty side dish...
like seasoned vegetables.
They were like...
father and mother I saw on TV.
They were like my role models.
They always welcomed me and let me have fun.
I visited the place since I had good memories.
It's like his hometown.
This place is so nice.
(A garden fills the front yard.)
Jae Kang's father built the place.
He designed a hanok house.
It's so nice.
(It has the sentimentality of the countryside.)
- I brought something tasty. - Why are your hands heavy?
You shouldn't have.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Thank you.
We left that spot...
since you were the main guest.
- Really? - Of course.
He returned in glory.
It's his hometown.
- Really? - You can see it now.
- I haven't visited in a while. - You're right.
When did you guys come?
- About an hour ago? - it has been an hour.
(As they talk, they enter the clay-colored house.)
It's nice. I love the loess walls.
- Jae Kang, we'll eat this. - Is it for us?
I'll put it in the fridge.
There's so much to eat today.
- Right? - Why did you buy so many things?
I'd like to give you a deep bow.
It has been over ten years.
Your friend's mom is like your mom.
- That's right. - Exactly.
I need to do it.
- You should do it too. - Here.
- Let's do it together. - All right.
- Shall we do it together? - Shall the three do it together?
(They're cute.)
My goodness.
That's when you do a deep bow.
Ma'am.
A deep bow.
Thank you.
- It's good to see you again. - It has been so long.
(Happy)
- It has been a while. - Yes.
Sit comfortably.
- Okay. - It has been a while.
- That's right. - My goodness.
I think it has been 10 years. Was it 12 years? Was it 15 years?
We met when Jae Kang got married...
in Busan.
- Right. We saw each other then. - Yes.
- Yes. - So it has been ten years.
- Ten years passed so fast. - That's right.
It has been that long.
Once you grow up,
you rarely get to see...
- your friend's parents. - That's right.
- I saw them often when I was young. - You do that when you're young.
- But once you grow up, - You rarely see them.
- It's hard to see them. - there has to be an occasion.
- May I stay overnight? - Of course.
- Stay overnight. - Build a fire in the furnace.
- Okay. - That's so nice.
You'll fall asleep easily.
Sir, is there anything I can help you with?
There are many tasks.
You guys should shovel today.
- You guys should shovel today. - Really?
- Yes. The yard. - There are some tasks.
I brought my trainers...
just in case.
- Three men should work. - That's right.
- I'll look around the house. - Okay.
- All right. - Okay.
We slept there before.
Yes. This is a study.
- My goodness. - It's a hobby room for calligraphy.
(It's the father's hobby room for calligraphy.)
He was a professor.
(He spots something.)
- Are those our photos? - Yes.
My goodness.
Be careful. Those are old photos of you.
Gosh, I was so ugly.
(He studies the photos.)
He printed out the photos.
(Gasping)
Do they bring back memories?
- When was it taken? - It's from 1998.
Yes. It's from 1998.
(In 1998, he was in 5th grade.)
Photos from that time have a certain vibe.
My goodness. Is it from ninth grade?
It's from middle school.
- He was handsome. - He was handsome.
I think that was when we got our graduation photos taken.
There are photos from our university days.
My goodness. A Von Dutch cap.
I can't believe it.
- A Von Dutch cap. - A Von Dutch cap.
Although he looks like that, he went to POSTECH.
He was the top of his class.
- No. - What does he look like?
He looks like a delinquent.
I guess your friends got good grades.
All of them got good grades.
Jae Kang was the vice president in middle school.
Hyung Jin studied architecture in Seoul National University.
- Really? - Both Jae Kang and Hyung Jin...
- work at nice companies. - Big companies.
Everyone got good grades except for me.
How did you befriend them?
- Smart kids stick together. - It's hard to befriend them.
- Smart kids stick together. - Isn't that a malicious question?
"How did you befriend them?"
But smart kids stick together.
That's right. It's a reasonable question.
It couldn't have been easy to befriend them.
Perhaps Jae Hyeon got good grades as well.
I received six points on my math exam.
- Then how... - That takes talent.
- How did you receive six points? - You need to be smart...
to receive such a score.
I bet you were bored...
- during the exam period. - I loved it.
- Why? - Weren't your friends busy?
They studied all the time.
I mean, when they received a difficult question,
they liked it. They laughed.
"This one looks fun." They were like that.
So all three of you enjoyed the exam period.
- I could go home early. - You liked going home early.
- Jae Hyeon was excited. - I guess it was possible...
since they were friends from elementary school.
We were friends because we remained close.
You guys bonded over soccer.
- We liked soccer. - There has to be a common interest.
Where did you get this photo?
I printed the Cyworld photos once.
This is me and this is you.
That's right.
That's right. The sticker photos looked like that.
The colors faded.
It's from that day.
- We went to a resort. - We went to a resort.
(The photos show the moments they spent together.)
He has always been handsome.
These photos bring back memories.
- Look at this. - Let's look at them again later.
Sure.
(Gasping)
It's a pencil sharpener.
- I haven't seen it in a while. - When you sharpen a pencil...
and smell the pencil dust, it's the best.
It's an antic.
- A pencil sharpener. - They don't sell it these days.
They don't sell big ones. They only sell small ones.
Jae Kang was the class president.
That's right.
He needed something like that.
Do we need to do a lot of shoveling?
Is there something we need to help them with?
Mom and Dad...
- have an appointment, - Will they head out?
- so they'll head out. - Okay.
This is your parents' field, right?
That's what my mom needs help on.
Do you see the grassy area?
We need to remove the grass and turn it into a garden.
Okay.
She wants us to remove the grass so that she can plant lettuce.
She wants us to remove rocks and such.
Jae Kang, I'll go and change.
Okay. Go and change.
All right. Let's get started.
What do we need to do?
- Can you shovel well? - I've never done it.
- You've never shoveled? - No.
- Should I put on the gloves? - The gloves are over there.
Put on the gloves, Jae Hyeon. You'll hurt your hands.
- What should I do? - Come here.
You see grass from here to there, right?
- The ditch. - Yes.
- The cherry blossom tree. - Yes. The ditch.
We'll turn over the plants and rocks...
and make it look like this.
(I see.)
Try it.
- You'll see once you try it. - Okay.
(Heave-ho)
- What? - It's nothing.
You're good. That's how you do it.
Am I doing this right?
- Here. - Am I doing this right?
(How do I do it?)
Dig in the shovel.
Turn it over like this.
(Turn over the plants and soil.)
- I see that Jae Kang is the leader. - That's right.
(The leader takes the initiative.)
All right.
(He copies Jae Kang and tries again.)
I can tell that it's his first time shoveling.
- It's his grip. - That's right.
You're grabbing the shovel like this.
- Is it wrong? - If you grab it like this,
you can't put your strength into it.
You'll only pull your forearm muscles.
- You need to grab it like this. - Like this?
- That's right. - Not like this?
Why is Na Rae going, "That's right?"
- Na Rae. - I heard...
that you did the military support for the civilian authorities.
I did that many times.
It was intense...
- during the farming season. - She was a noncommissioned officer.
I think Jae Hyeon is tired already.
My pants are falling down.
(I'm not tired.)
- Shall I tie them in the back? - Would you do that?
- Good? - Yes. It's comfortable.
Really?
(Panting)
(Struggling)
(Between the two dads who are working hard)
(Turning)
- Oh, no. - What was that?
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
My goodness.
Why is it hard?
- It's hard. - It's hard indeed.
My back hurts so much.
Use your legs, not your back.
That's right. Lower your legs.
Like this?
Jae Hyeon.
Like this,
use your legs.
That's how you do it. It'll hurt less.
(Jae Hyeon does his best.)
(He's sweating buckets.)
- Oh, my. - It was so hard.
Oh, my.
Your legs are shaking already.
No. It's because I drove a lot.
Step on it and lift.
- Turn it over. - That's right.
- When Jae Hyeon shovels, - Yes?
it looks strenuous.
(It looks especially strenuous.)
I think the muscles you use are different from what others use.
These muscles are for fashion.
- My goodness. - These muscles are for fashion.
Oh, no. He's so weak.
You're doing well, Jae Hyeon.
- My goodness. - You're sweating so much.
(The two dads don't get tired.)
Look at Jae Hyeon's eyes. He seems sick.
- Oh, no. - What is he going to do?
My goodness.
- I'm exhausted, Jae Kang. - What?
Good luck.
(Chuckling)
What is he going to do?
(What is Jae Hyeon going to do?)
He works really hard.
Doing well isn't important.
- It's good to see. - Yes. You just need to do it.
He works hard.
You still did a lot, Jae Hyeon.
- He did a lot. - Right.
(Sweating)
It's been a while to do something like this, right, Rio?
- It's been a while, right? - It has been a while.
Rio? Is that his nickname?
It's because he looks like Super Mario.
- He does look like him. - So that's why.
- He does look like him. - He does look like Him.
I called him Rio more than his name.
- Rio. - Rio.
Should we take a break?
Cucumbers are great.
That was amazing.
They're great when you need to get hydrated.
Cucumbers taste great.
- I'm reminded of that. - What?
There were older girls in school that liked Jae Hyeon.
- Right. - Right.
The older girls came to the classroom for Jae Hyeon.
- Right. - So that's possible?
He refused to go out with them,
- so they dragged him out. - No way.
Hold on. Has anyone been dragged out...
beside Jae Hyeon?
I was dragged out by the older guys.
- Oh, right. - What happened?
What did they do after dragging you out?
They called me out during lunch.
Why?
They were sitting down just like we are right now.
I was right in the middle of them.
"Hey, Ahn Jae Hyeon!" "Yes?"
They didn't even say anything about wanting to date me.
Then why did they call you out?
I was just told to sit in between them.
That was all that happened.
I can now talk about this with a smile,
but they were really scary back then.
I still feel jealous.
Right.
You guys hid behind the curtains.
I thought it was a joke.
Being dragged out for a month as a joke?
How is that possible?
- The cucumber... - I feel better.
- charged me up. - Right.
- We're done. - What?
Just flatten out that part with your hands.
The easy part is left now.
These are carrot seeds. Place 2 to 3 of them.
You did a lot of work.
Those are tomatoes.
The seedlings for tomatoes.
Should we meet in winter?
That sounds good.
- Let's water them now. - Okay.
Here.
(Swaying)
- It's because he has long legs. - Gosh!
You'll be great at badminton with that kind of flexibility.
(He seems to have the talent.)
(The ground is soft.)
The ground is soft.
(That's a relief.)
What do we do now?
- Are we done? - We need to water them.
- Give them a lot of water. - Okay.
That's good.
The water is coming out well.
- That's perfect. - It can be controlled.
You're doing well.
- How am I doing? - You're doing well.
Are you two really friends?
Hold on.
After he became a father,
- he changed. - Right.
- He changed. - Fathers speak differently.
(You're doing well, my Jae Hyeon.)
(Feeling proud)
There you go. Use your tall height.
Great.
That's enough. Done!
Let's eat.
- We're done? - We're done.
- We need to make a fire. - We do.
How should it be done?
This needs to be moved first.
This cauldron is heavy.
(Jae Kang lifts the cauldron.)
It isn't heavy.
- Lift this up. - I'll get it.
"Lift this up."
That's how fathers speak to their sons.
It has to be placed at the side.
It has to be used when we use the ax.
- Right. - It can be placed later.
Where will the ax be used?
It will be used right there.
(Placing the tire just as his father told him to)
It would be better to cook out here, right?
That sounds great.
Where should the fire face?
(Let's cook in the big yard.)
Let's set the table, Jae Hyeon.
(Following)
- Gosh. - You do everything you're told.
Jae Kang is really charming.
- I'm sorry, but are you his son? - "Let's set the table, Jae Hyeon."
- Rio is just watching. - Right.
Bring out the barbecue that is over there, Rio.
(Gosh!)
(He does what he is told to do right away.)
- Gosh. It does feel that way. - He's charismatic.
- He has all the authority. - Right.
I didn't know this. So this is how we are together.
(He didn't realize the father-and-son relationship.)
How is this unfolded?
What?
I ask Jae Kang too many questions, right?
- You can ask things. - Well,
- you can ask the boss things. - Right.
It's nice that you're asking about things you don't know about.
He definitely is your friend, right?
He is my friend.
After that, pull the ring.
- The ring? - There you go.
His compliments made me work.
- He knows how to lead people. - Right.
Try setting it up on your own.
I'll bring out something to clean it with.
Isn't Jae Kang good at grilling meat?
He should be the best amongst us.
Right.
(Jae Kang cleans the table to complete the table setup.)
Should I split the firewood?
Can you do it without my help?
Right.
(I can definitely do it on my own, Dad!)
How is the firewood split, Jae Kang?
Place it down and strike it well.
- Isn't it placed here? - Right.
- Put it down. - Get this down for me.
Throw it down.
You two might hurt your backs.
(The two sons help each other when they are in need.)
- Try it with this first. - Do I just strike it down?
Strike it down. Give it a try first.
(Tapping)
You can't do it like that, Jae Hyeon.
I'll show you.
- Is this not right? - It is, but...
- Brought down like this. - Here.
- Kian84 is good at that. - Right.
- The grains go down like this. - Right.
Then you should strike it down right here.
How many pieces should it be split into?
Around 3 to 4 pieces instead of just 2 pieces.
(Striking down)
It isn't easy to split firewood.
It isn't easy to do.
- I'll show you, Rio. - Okay.
It's right here.
(Missing)
My gosh.
Gosh.
- He's struggling. - Gosh.
It will turn dark before he gets done.
This is too tough.
- It must be oakwood. - What?
Give it to me.
That isn't how it's done.
(It won't work.)
I should be careful too.
- I think he'll be good at it. - This is...
Here's the father.
- Gosh! Look at that! - That's how it's done.
- There you go! - Gosh!
- He's good. - You have to strike it down.
Here's the father.
You look different, Jae Kang. You're a true father.
(Striking down with the power of the father)
(I will do it like that too!)
I'll try.
Try hitting it right in the middle.
Right.
- Gosh. - He has no strength at all.
What did I do wrong?
Servant84 has the skills.
After observing him,
- what do you think he did wrong? - Well...
(I am Servant84.)
- I was surprised by this. - Right.
(The servant who is talented in splitting firewood)
- It isn't done with strength. - Right.
- After lifting it up, - You strike it down?
you have to bring it down with force.
As you bring it down, you have to grab the bottom of the ax...
and strike it.
It's done with a sudden force, right?
- With the sudden speed? - It isn't done with strength.
It's done by skill.
Right. Be careful.
You might hurt your leg.
- Be careful. - Be careful.
You'll hurt your leg. Be careful.
(I believe in you, my son!)
(Look at me, Dad!)
- Be careful. - Be careful.
(I'll show you my power!)
- Gosh! - Hold on.
Oh, no!
(Swaying around because of the heavy ax)
- Gosh! - My gosh.
- It was heavy. - Look at that scarecrow.
(Swaying)
- Hold on. - "Creak."
Watch out.
Be careful.
(His body sways around helplessly by the heavy ax.)
(This is strange.)
(Why is my body like this?)
Why am I moving like that?
Just do it your way, Jae Hyeon.
Don't use the method you were told to use.
(Okay! I'll use my own method!)
(Bumping)
This is sad to watch.
(The ax doesn't even go through the firewood any more.)
(Breathing in)
(Bumping)
(I won't give up!)
Grab the bottom of the ax!
(Doing a back somersault)
Did you get a muscle cramp?
(Gosh, Jae Hyeon!)
Ju Seung got a muscle cramp.
Call me if you need help with something.
- Really? - I'll go to you.
I feel anxious to let you do things on your own.
It's because he doesn't have much experience.
You can grill the meat instead.
Right. I can grill the meat.
- Right. - Each person has their own role.
Right. We all have our own roles.
We'll get the clams along with the water.
- I'll grill the meat for us. - Let's see the meat.
Gosh.
- Brisket. - It looks delicious.
- Neck chain. - Gosh, it looks delicious.
- There's so much meat. - There's more.
That must be really filling.
- How does it look? - It looks great.
I'll grill the meat.
It has to be grilled well.
Jae Hyeon is great at cooking.
- It's working. There you go. - Gosh!
- That's nice. - Gosh!
- Gosh! - It's working.
That looks good.
(The meat gets grilled quickly.)
The fire lit up at once.
- Right. - How does it look?
- It looks good. - Right.
It looks tender.
- Let's try it first. - Right.
(Let's try it before it goes cold.)
- Great work. - Gosh.
Cheers!
(They hold up their cold beer glasses.)
- Cheers! - Cheers!
That's great.
The weather looks perfect.
Gosh, this is insane. Try this first.
(Try the meat.)
- I'll give it a try. - This is the first one. Neck chain.
Neck chain?
(Dipping it in salt)
- The owner... - Yes?
(The first bite of meat after working)
The neck chain must taste clean.
(I'm jealous.)
told me to eat the meat in order.
(Eyes opening wide)
That tasted like something in between tenderloin and sirloin.
It was delicious.
- You're enjoying it. - It's good.
(Feeling proud as his friends are enjoying it)
- Eat a lot. - Okay.
- We have a lot to eat. - Right.
(I'll eat a lot.)
That was good.
(Grilling with care)
That looks amazing.
Here's the second cut.
- I think they will all taste good. - Give it a try.
The meat is getting grilled better and better.
It gets grilled nice and slow.
I'm placing two pieces right now.
- Jae Hyeon. - Yes?
You feel affectionate. You grill the meat for them too.
- You're the best at grilling meat. - Right.
- That's a relief. - It's fine not being able to...
split firewood.
I should do be able to do one thing at least.
(Eating the meat grilled by Jae Hyeon quickly)
- I think this is the best cut. - Gosh.
It just needs to be dipped in salt.
- The inside skirt tastes good. - It's good.
I'll grill this next to it.
- That's the ribeye cap? - Yes.
- It really looks like a cap. - Right.
That's the best cut.
- Right. It's amazing. - It's amazing.
We did do a lot of work.
It was tough. My arms are cramping up.
It was tough to work on the field, right?
It was tough.
- It didn't feel tough for me. - Right.
What a joke.
(They're best buddies.)
It was tough for your friends' hearts.
It was just...
You fell as your legs gave in.
No.
Fashion muscles.
(His two legs kept tangling up.)
I'm always like that.
- I see. - I didn't feel tired.
There's nothing hard for you in life.
- That's not true, you punk. - What's hard for you?
- Things are hard for me too. - What's hard for you?
It is hard for me too.
To be honest, you can't say life is hard in front of Jae Hyeon.
(To be honest, you can't say life is hard in front of Jae Hyeon.)
Right.
(Sighing)
Rio makes great comments from the side.
He cuts in well.
- Rio... - He's good at that.
- times his jabs well. - Right.
(He feels dizzy after getting hit by Rio.)
Jae Hyeon went missing for a while.
- Right. - Right.
- He didn't answer our calls. - He didn't even contact us.
He didn't want to see us being happy in life.
Right.
(He didn't want to see us being happy in life.)
- They are best buddies. - Right.
They are able to talk about that because they are friends.
- You're getting emotional, right? - Yes. I'm tearing up.
Let's try this.
(Let's forget about everything and have some more meat.)
- The ribeye cap! - Gosh, here's the main cut.
This is the best part.
(The finishing touch with the ribeye cap)
(Amazed)
(They pause for a while as soon as it goes in their mouths.)
- Which is the best cut for you? - This is good.
- This is the best cut. - Really?
There's no doubt with the ribeye cap.
- It just melts in your mouth. - Gosh.
(Feeling jealous)
That looks delicious.
- Should we have the crab? - Should we?
- There were crabs too. - That's an amazing course.
(The seafood course prepared by Jae Kang)
Gosh!
(Steaming with the scent of the sea)
That looks delicious.
I heard it was good when you grilled it with mayonnaise in the shell.
That's right.
So that's how it's grilled.
- They are full of roe right now. - Right.
They will be out of season soon.
- Jae Kang... - Will we have it right away?
No. He'll work on them first.
- With the mayonnaise? - Right.
- It's closed up again? - Right.
- Gosh, that looks great. - Gosh.
(It goes on the grill after being closed up.)
(Opening up boldly)
- Gosh - The K-Dad.
The dad with two sons definitely feels different.
Right.
- Dad! - Yes?
(Dad!)
- I'll give it a try. - Give it a try, Jae Hyeon.
(I'll try too, Dad.)
- He really sounds like your dad. - Right.
I like that.
- I'll give it a try. - Give it a try, Jae Hyeon.
(Give it a try, Jae Hyeon.)
- Should I open the shell for you? - I opened it.
Gosh.
Gosh, look at this.
(Son Jae Hyeon managed to open up the shell.)
- Gosh, that looks good. - Check out the roe.
- Squeeze the mayonnaise? - Yes. Squeeze it.
That's right. There you go.
- Close it? - Close it.
- Like this? - Yes.
Then place it on the grill.
Close the grill next.
What is it?
(The blue crab mayo gets slightly cooked.)
- Should we grill the clams? - Should we do that too?
Let's eat everything we have.
There are grilled clams too?
- The pen shells are the main ones. - Right.
- Why are they so big? - I bought the big ones.
(Moving busily)
There are red scallops.
- Scallops are good. - Gosh, that's hot.
Jae Kang has quick hands.
I do.
Do you want to try the crab?
- Can it be eaten? - It can.
They were steamed.
(That looks good.)
The crabs were grilled one more time with the mayonnaise.
- That looks delicious. - Check out the roe.
(Plump)
Gosh, that looks good.
Just the mayonnaise has to melt.
- It looks great. - It has melted.
- Let's eat. - It will taste great.
(The blue crab has turned juicy in a flash.)
It didn't feel heavy at all.
Really? I thought it would feel heavy.
- Gosh. - It tastes light.
It looks great.
It looks great. Try it.
Thank you.
I'll give this to you, Jae Hyeon.
They are in season, so they taste really good.
Right.
It's good, isn't it?
- It's delicious. - Gosh.
(Hyung Jin scoops it up with a spoon.)
He takes good care of his friends.
- He's definitely a father. - Right.
Here.
(Focused)
Gosh, check out the roe.
(Taking a bite off the crab)
(Crunching)
You're eating well today.
- Right. I'm eating everything. - Gosh.
(Our Jae Hyeon is eating well.)
(Opening wide)
(Thank you, Dad.)
It looks like he's there with his two sons.
- Right. - Rio is a father too.
- Rio is a father too. - Jae Kang has two sons.
- Are these two his sons? - That's what it's like.
It isn't easy to feed your friend like that.
Right.
I think it'll be a good idea to be adopted to his family.
- They don't look like friends. - You've already...
- established that relationship. - Jae Kang is like a mother bird.
- This is really good. - Let's do this.
- Making a toast with this? - That looks delicious.
(Making a toast with their spoons)
Gosh.
(The father is satisfied too.)
- It's good. - Right.
It's good.
(Getting up)
Do you want to try the razor shell?
- Gosh. - Give it a try.
- Gosh. - It should be eaten with the juice.
- It's good. - It's good.
It tastes like the spaghetti alle vongole.
I like razor shells the most.
We'll grill the shrimp a bit more to be safe.
If you were to be born again in the future,
you would marry your wife again, right?
Of course.
- Great. That was a quick response. - Of course, I should.
Would you get married when you were born again?
(Would you get married when you were born again?)
(What?)
- He's definitely from SNU. - As expected.
People from SNU are sharp.
- He's just my style. - He has...
- everything calculated. - Well,
the first answer was just for the build-up.
A build-up for your answer.
- Gosh. - That was sharp.
He cut in right away when he was vulnerable.
- That was sharp. - He's definitely smart.
You asked first.
You asked if I was going to marry my current wife again.
Ask me when I have a wife.
(Getting back at him)
Jae Hyeon has become a lot brighter than before.
Right.
When are you talking about?
(Bright)
(A 2nd hit)
- Rio is tough. - Gosh!
(Thinking)
(Peeking)
When was the most difficult time in your life, Jae Hyeon?
Gosh, he finished him off.
He looks really proud after saying what he has to say.
That friend has the face of Yoo Se Yoon.
Right!
(That friend has the face of Yoo Se Yoon.)
- Right. - Right.
It felt like it was Se Yoon.
- You're right. - He always teases people.
He has the face of a comedian.
(Rio teases people well.)
He teases people just like Se Yoon.
We are turning 40 soon.
What will you do when you turn 40?
- Is there something you want to do? - What are you going to do?
- Me? - Yes.
I'm going to wait for your third child.
- I'll wait for your first child. - Gosh!
The baby must look adorable.
Of course. It's Jae Hyeon's child.
You give out the bait really well.
Right!
Shall we make a toast for Jae Hyeon's new beginning?
- Sure. - For Jae Hyeon's new beginning.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
(For Jae Hyeon's new beginning)
As a man who lives alone in Seongsu-dong,
(Honorary man who lives alone in Seongsu-dong)
I thought that I was living the perfect life alone.
But today, I was able to forget about my age.
I spent the day in my brightest form possible.
How should I put it? Whenever I meet my friends,
I always return back to the age when I first met them.
I will always feel grateful for these friends...
as I spend the rest of my life with them.
(I will spend the rest of my life in my brightest form.)
This was the best memory I had with you guys.
- You guys told me this later. - What?
It was when I didn't know anything.
You guys said, "Jae Hyeon must be struggling right now."
"Let's gather some money to help out Jae Hyeon."
I learned about that a while later.
I felt grateful for that.
(His friends wanted to help him out when he was struggling.)
I think we said that when we were drunk.
- I don't remember that. - Same here.
That was when we were 23.
It will never end in a touching atmosphere.
- They are truly best buddies. - I am still struggling.
I'm struggling too.
What are you talking about? You work for a big company.
You make a lot of money.
(Everyone seems fine as they're constantly making jokes.)
A big company?
- Let's go inside and chat. - Okay.
(Let's Stay the Same)
(Next episode)
(Jang Woo's appetite is strong as usual.)
(Giant cut of chuck flap tail)
(Who are his guests?)
(The rising actor of "Weak Hero Class 2", Ryeo Un)
(Lee Know of Stray Kids, the global idol stars)
(The three are all born in the Year of the Tiger.)
(Let's have some beef, Tigers.)
(Impressed)
(Top-quality Korean beef)
(He went to Hoengseong for his younger friends.)
(Slicing)
(I do things properly.)
(Perfect)
Right.
It's insane, isn't it?
(The beef brought by the older one)
(Touched)
(The hunt was a big hit.)
(Brimming with the energy of tigers)
(Let my present intensify the energy.)
(Roar)
(How "tighter" this looks.)
(Feeling proud)
(With their overflowing energy, they exercise together.)
(The friendship of the three brothers deepens.)
(Give Me Meat, and I Shall Spare You)
(Someone wakes up in a dark room.)
(Throwing on a gown while looking cool)
(Whose house...)
(is this?)
(The house has a cozy, sophisticated vibe in spades.)
(Full of artistic furniture with sentimental values)
(Filled with unique props)
(It's been 8 years since I began living alone.)
(I'm a musical actor, Kai.)
(As he performed passionately in major musicals,)
(he established himself as a fail-proof actor.)
(There's a sense of warmth in his baritone voice.)
(This irreplaceable actor also mastered popera.)
(He begins his morning with coffee.)
(He reads newspapers, books, and scripts,)
(leading an analog life fueled by words.)
(He also clips an article from the newspaper.)
(Tenor)
(An elegant day with Artist Kai and his cat, Tenor)
(He's dressed in a comfortable outfit.)
(Is he going out?)
(He enters the house with familiar ease.)
The thought of running away brings me relief.
(It's my house on Jeju Island.)
(Yes, I need this place.)
(Off to My Sanctuary)